pixate.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy | Pixate

_Version 1.0.0, published March 12, 2013._

## 1\. Introduction

Pixate, Inc. (“Pixate”, “our”, “us” or “we”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive from users of [](http://pixate.com/)[http://pixate.com](http://pixate.com/) (this “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through this Site. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. You are advised to consult this policy regularly for any changes. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Pixate Terms of Use.

As used in this policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within the United States or internationally.

## 2\. Information Collection and Use

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our Site, software, services, features and content, to administer your use of the Site (together, the “Service”) and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

### 2.1 Personally Identifiable Information

When you (i) register with us through the Site and create an Account to become a Member, (ii) submit your resume to apply for a position with Pixate, (iii) make a purchase via the Service, (iv) submit an inquiry or request for more information via the Service, (v) submit an app you created via the Service, (vi) register any software you downloaded via the Service, or (vii) post or comment on a blog or forum via the Service, we will ask you for personally identifiable information. This refers to information about you that can be used to contact or identify you

(“Personal Information”). Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, company, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses. We use your Personal Information mainly to provide the Service and administer your inquiries.

We also collect the other information that you provide as part of registration and your use of the Service (e.g., without limitation, software serial number, zip code (on its own) and individual preferences) (“Non-Identifying Information”).

We use your Personal Information (in some cases, in conjunction with your Non-Identifying Information) mainly to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries.

Certain Non-Identifying Information would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers (for example, combining your zip code with your street address) in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other non-identifying information (for example, your viewing preferences). We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other Pixate Users (defined below) to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how our Site and Service are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically, for instance to deliver a product to you according to your preferences or restrictions.

We also use your Personal Information to contact you with Pixate newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or opt-out of receiving such communications via the Service. (See “Changing or Deleting Information,” below.)

## 3\. Log Data

When you visit the Site, whether as a Pixate Member or a non-registered user just browsing (any of these, a “Pixate User”), our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”).

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration, to increase our Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs. We also use this information to verify that visitors to the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests. We do not treat Log Data as Personal Information or use it in association with other Personal Information, though we may aggregate, analyze and evaluate such information for the same purposes as stated above regarding other Non-Identifying Information.

## 4\. Cookies

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by Pixate Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Service and then close your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service.

## 5\. Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as “phishing” are of great concern to Pixate. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your Account information, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication. For more information about phishing, visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website.

## 6\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

### 6.1 Pixate Users

If you choose to comment or post a question on our blog or forum or if you submit an app you created via the Service, other users of the Service will see the content of your comment, question or app, along with your name and email address, if you choose to provide an email address. Providing your email address and full name is voluntary, and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with other Pixate Users. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information.

### 6.2 Aggregate Information and Non-Identifying Information

We may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your Personal Information.

### 6.3 Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Site-related services (e.g., without limitation, maintenance services, database management, payment processing, web analytics and improvement of the Site’s features) or to assist us in analyzing how our Site and Service are used. These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### 6.4 Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

Pixate cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Pixate or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

### 6.5 Business Transfers

Pixate may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy.

## 7\. Changing or Deleting Your Information

All Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information provided during registration by contacting us. If you completely delete all such information, then your Account may become deactivated. If you would like us to delete your Account in our system, please contact us at [members@pixate.com](mailto:members@pixate.com) with a request that we delete your Personal Information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honor your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

## 8\. Security

Pixate is very concerned with safeguarding your information. The security of your personal information is important to us. But remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). In some cases, we also encrypt sensitive information where it is stored on our systems.

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored “personal data” (as defined in applicable state statutes on security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

## 9\. Links to Other Sites and Services

Our Site contains links to other websites, online services or applications (each a “Third Party Service”), e.g.: You may be brought to the website of our third party payment processor. If you click on another third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website or online service. The fact that we link to a Third Party Service is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over Third Party Services. Such Third Party Services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other websites and online services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other Third Party Services you visit.

## 10\. Our Policy Toward Children

This Site is not directed to individuals under 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@pixate.com](mailto:privacy@pixate.com). If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@pixate.com](mailto:privacy@pixate.com).

  * Privacy Policy
  * Terms of Use

  *  __Pixate Blog
